Arts and Sciences, College of; Records ua600
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1965-2011; 4; 10.33 cubic ft.
  - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Empire State Youth Orchestra, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Diversity Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Actions, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Personnel Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Personnel Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Personnel Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Personnel Committee cases under consideration, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Diversity committee, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Arts management Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Instructional Technology Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Computing Subcommittee, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - College By-Laws, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - College Council, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Fellowships, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Awards for Undergraduate Research, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - University Publications and Funding Sources, 1988-1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Racial Concerns Committee, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fipse, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Multi Cultural Concerns Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Students at Risk Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Peebles Island Internships, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - College Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - College Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Edith O. Wallace day, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Suny Benevolent Association Grants, Spring 1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Suny Benevolent Association Grants, Fall 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Suny Benevolent Association Grants, Spring 1992 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Suny Benevolent Association Grants, Fall 1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Thayer Fellowships, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - USIA Proposal Yugoslavia, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - USIA Proposal Italy, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - USIA Proposal Costa Rica, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - USIA Bulgaria, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Institute for Arts in Education, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Division of Performing Arts, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PAC, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - D.A. Program, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - D.A. in Humanistic Studies, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Arts in Education, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Linguistics & Cognitive Science, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Linguistics & Cognitive Science (Lig. & Cog. Sci.), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CHFA & CSBS Joint Diversity, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Linguistics & Cognitive Science, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Departmental Degree Candidate Recognition Programs, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- College of Sciences and Mathematics, 1963-2011; 5; 7.17 cubic ft.
  Materials in this series have been maintained in their original order.
  This series documents the administration of the College of Sciences and Mathematics. Series contains annual reports, graduate and undergraduate program reviews, comittee meeting minutes, grant proposals, files of various chairs and departments, memoranda, recruitment plans, degree and program proposals, three- and five-year plans for the college and departments. Some materials in this series predate its creation as a separate college and were likely retained from the period in which it was a Division within the College of Arts and Sciences.
- College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1967-2011; 6; 11.66 cubic ft.
  Series contains 5" floppy disks.
  This series documents the administration of the College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, particularly between the college's founding in 1978 and 1993. Series contains correspondence and letterbooks, graduate and undergraduate program reviews, three- and five-year plans, committee meeting agendas and minutes, task force and committee reports, degree and academic program proposals, faculty handbooks, administrative files related to the management of institutes including the Institutute for Research on Women and the Institute for Mesoamerican Studies. Some materials in this series predate its creation as a separate college and were likely retained from the period in which it was a Division within the College of Arts and Sciences.
- Center for the Humanities Advisory Board, 1984-1988; 7; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have arranged chronologically.
  This series documents the administration of the Center for the Humanities, a University Center under the control of the College of Humanities and Fine Arts which put on conferences, seminars and fellowship programs. Series includes Director's Reports, memoranda, correspondence, advisory board meeting minutes and proposals for faculty seminars.
- College of Arts and Sciences Ad Hoc Committee on Harassment, 1991-1996; 8; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Materials in this series have been arranged chronologically.
  This series documents the drafting of the ad hoc committee's report on new procedures regarding allegations of harassment. Series includes the final report, drafts and revisions to the report, correspondence with the committee chair, sexual harassment policy documents from other universities, as well as publications produced by the University at Albany.